const questions = {
  question1: {
    question: "Test 1",
    answer: 4,
    button1: "Wrong answer",
    button2: "Wrong answer",
    button3: "Wrong answer",
    button4: "Right answer",
  },
  question2: {
    question: "Test 2",
    answer: 2,
    button1: "Wrong answer",
    button2: "Right answer",
    button3: "Wrong answer",
    button4: "Wrong answer",
  },
  question3: {
    question: "Test 3",
    answer: 1,
    button1: "Right answer",
    button2: "Wrong answer",
    button3: "Wrong answer",
    button4: "Wrong answer",
  },
  question4: {
    question: "Test 4",
    answer: 3,
    button1: "Wrong answer",
    button2: "Wrong answer",
    button3: "Right answer",
    button4: "Wronganswer",
  },
  question5: {
    question: "Test 5",
    answer: 3,
    button1: "Wrong answer",
    button2: "Wrong answer",
    button3: "Right answer",
    button4: "Wrong answer",
  },
  question6: {
    question: "Test 6",
    answer: 4,
    button1: "Wrong answer",
    button2: "Wrong answer",
    button3: "Wrong answer",
    button4: "Right answer",
  },
  question7: {
    question: "Test 7",
    answer: 1,
    button1: "Right answer",
    button2: "Wrong answer",
    button3: "Wrong answer",
    button4: "Wrong answer",
  },
  question8: {
    question: "Test 8",
    answer: 1,
    button1: "Right answer",
    button2: "Wrong answer",
    button3: "Wrong answer",
    button4: "Wrong answer",
  },
  question9: {
    question: "Test 9",
    answer: 2,
    button1: "Wrong answer",
    button2: "Right answer",
    button3: "Wrong answer",
    button4: "Wrong answer",
  },
  question10: {
    question: "Test 10",
    answer: 4,
    button1: "Wrong answer",
    button2: "Wrong answer",
    button3: "Wrong answer",
    button4: "Right answer",
  },
};
